b00kmarks.com 2014-09-11

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Respecting users' privacy is a key value for b00kmarks. To learn about what personal information b00kmarks collects and how it may be used, please read b00kmarks 's privacy policy here below. If you have any questions, please contact b00kmarks user support. Thank you. 

We will comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and any other applicable data protection legislation. By registering for the b00kmarks services you consent to our using and/or disclosing your personal information for the following purposes: 

\- providing, or arranging for third parties to provide, help desk facilities which may be available to you which may involve disclosing your personal information to third parties solely for those purposes; 

\- providing, or arranging for third parties to provide, any additional services you request from us; 

\- as required or permitted by law from time to time. 

We will not use your personal data for marketing other b00kmarks products and services or any third party products and services without having given you the opportunity to opt out of such marketing opportunities. 

We are committed to protecting your right to privacy. Any information you provide to us will be held on computers that are based in Hong Kong. We collect information about our users in order to help continually improve the b00kmarks services. We also use the information you provide us to enter into commercial arrangements, including the sale of advertising space, which allow the b00kmarks service to remain free for all our users. We will always adhere to the Data Protection Act 1998 (UK) in relation to our use of your information and any other applicable data protection laws. This Privacy Policy relates only to our use of the information you provide us and your use of b00kmarks and does not extend to your use of the Internet other than b00kmarks. 

### What data do we collect from you?

We collect the personal data you provide when you register for b00kmarks services with us. We also collect any other personal data that you provide when using b00kmarks, for example, to enter competitions. We also use cookie technology to monitor which areas of b00kmarks you prefer. The information obtained from the cookies is not stored alongside your personal data and will only be used on an anonymous, aggregated basis. We may also hold information relating to any transactions that you enter into with us or any of our third party retail partners. 

We use the advertising agencies to serve ads when you visit b00kmarks Sites. These companies may use information about your visits to b00kmarks Sites, including the searches you conduct while on b00kmarks Sites. None of this information is used to identify you personally. This information is used to present you with relevant advertisements on other Websites that you may visit. 

### What we do with the data we collect from you?

We may use the personal information we collect from you to build up a profile of your interests and preferences. This information may be disclosed to other b00kmarks group companies and carefully selected third parties and/or used to make you aware of products or services that you may find of interest. If you do not wish to have your details passed on to carefully selected third parties or if you do not wish to receive unsolicited mailings from us, you may anytime opt out in the user profile section of b00kmarks. 

### Third Party Advertising

The advertisements appearing on the b00kmarks services are delivered to you by ourselves and by advertising agencies. Information about your visit to b00kmarks, such as the number of times you have viewed a particular advertisement (but not information about you, such as your name, address or any other personal information) is used to decide which advertisements to serve to you. 

In the course of serving advertisements to you cookie technology may be used, but such cookies will not be used to collect any personally identifiable information about you. 

### Private Communications

It is our policy to respect the privacy of private communications. We will not intentionally inspect the contents of private communications sent or received using the b00kmarks Portal except as required or permitted to do so by law. 

### Children and b00kmarks 

We do not specifically collect information about children and believe that children should always get the consent of their parents before giving out any personal information. Where children are specifically encouraged to participate within b00kmarks, they will always be advised that they should seek parental permission before they continue with the activity. We recommend that parents actively participate and where possible monitor their children's use of b00kmarks.   
Keeping your details private 

The use of Newsgroups or Forums/Chat, either within the b00kmarks Portal or on the Internet, is at your own risk. This may result in you receiving unsolicited messages from other parties who have picked up your details from such services. Further, do not forget that if you enter your details in the b00kmarks Users Directory they will be generally available to all b00kmarks users. 

### Disclosure of data in accordance with law

We may need to disclose your data to appropriate persons where required or permitted by law (for example, to law enforcement authorities in relation to the investigation of a suspected criminal offence). 

### Changing contact details

You can update or amend your contact details at any time from within the b00kmarks Portal. If you have any questions about the use of your personal data or if you wish to know how you can inspect or correct other personal data we may hold please contact us at: 

Populis Ireland Limited,   
Grand Mill Quay, Block 2 Barrow Street Dublin 4 (Ireland)   
Phone Number: +353 (0)1 4912050   
Vat Number IE 9573107U 

### Changes to the Policy

We may need to amend the Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such amendment will take effect as soon as it is posted on the b00kmarks Portal. You are therefore encouraged to familiarise yourself with the Privacy Policy on a regular basis. The Privacy Policy will always be easily accessible online throughout b00kmarks.
